<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
	<!--Sexuality card-->
	<SizeQueenQuirk>
		{pawn} really likes larger penises. {pawn} gets satisfied if a penis is larger than {pawn}'s vagina, or if its at least 1/4 their body size.
	</SizeQueenQuirk>
	<KnotLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} enjoys a penis that has a large bulge somewhere in it. And the though of it getting stuck inside makes {pawn_objective} go nuts.
	</KnotLoverQuirk>
	<FlareLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} loves a dick with a head that can grow twice its size.
	</FlareLoverQuirk>
	<SheathLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} loves when the flaccid penis fits neatly inside a sheath, hiding its shape and size completely. Each new sheath holds a new surprise for {pawn_objective}.
	</SheathLoverQuirk>
	<BarbsLoverQuirk>
		While not a masochist because of this, {pawn} really enjoys the sharp barbs some genitals have. How they feel on their hands, tongue, inside...{pawn} loves all of it.
	</BarbsLoverQuirk>
	<PointyLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} has a thing for dicks that are pointy. They are just so much easier to put in.
	</PointyLoverQuirk>
	<RidgeLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} loves the feel ridges, bumps, and creases create during sex.
	</RidgeLoverQuirk>
	<SlitLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} loves when a vagina suddenly produces a penis. Not knowing if a penis will come out or not, gets {pawn}'s gears going fast.
	</SlitLoverQuirk>
	<RigidLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} loves a penis that is always ready for action, one that never goes limp.
	</RigidLoverQuirk>
	<HemiLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} loves penises that have more than one member. The possibilities of having group sex with a single partner is endearing to {pawn}.
	</HemiLoverQuirk>
	<TentacleLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} loves things that grasp, contort, wiggle and twist. Even if its a penis. Specially if it is a penis.
	</TentacleLoverQuirk>	
	<HumanLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} has a fixation over the features of human genitals. The smooth shaft fully covered in skin, the red-ish head at the tip, the way it hangs free when flaccid. All of these are amazing features in {pawn}'s eyes.	
	</HumanLoverQuirk>
	<ArtificialLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} has a kink for prosthetics, specifically genital ones. It does not matter how crude, as long as it is man-made.
	</ArtificialLoverQuirk>
	<SolidLoverFetish>
		{pawn} realy loves when the parts are so hard, they do not budge in the lightest. Between a piece of wood and a hard dick, {pawn} would refer the wood.
	</SolidLoverFetish>
	<FickleQuirk>
		{pawn} has very fluid preferences, so they love when a genital can change sizes at will.
	</FickleQuirk>
	<GlowLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} has a kink for parts that emit light, like glowsticks and neon. It does not matter if its penis, a nipple, even an anus.
	</GlowLoverQuirk>
	<MuscleLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} adores big, defined muscles. {pawn} gets satisfied if their partner has the hulk body type.
	</MuscleLoverQuirk>
	<FatLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} loves some meat in his bone. {pawn} gets satisfied if their partner has the fat body type.
	</FatLoverQuirk>
	<ThinLoverQuirk>
		{pawn} loves some bone in his meat. {pawn} gets satisfied if their partner has the thin body type.
	</ThinLoverQuirk>
</LanguageData>