<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <GolemPenis.label>mineral penis</GolemPenis.label>
  <GolemPenis.description>A hollow shaft made of a hard mineral material, like rock or crystal.</GolemPenis.description>
  <!-- Ghost -->

  <GhostPenis.label>immaterial penis</GhostPenis.label>
  <GhostPenis.description>A translucent, almost intangible penis. Some parts of it seem to be composed of a bluish-white "flame", that is very cold. Touching it sends chills down the spine.</GhostPenis.description>

  <GhostVagina.label>immaterial vagina</GhostVagina.label>
  <GhostVagina.description>A translucent, almost intangible vagina. Internally, it seems to be composed of a bluish-white "flame", that is very cold. Penetrating it sends chills down the spine.</GhostVagina.description>

  <GhostBreasts.label>immaterial breasts</GhostBreasts.label>
  <GhostBreasts.description>A translucent, almost intangible pair of breasts. The nipples seems to be composed of a bluish-white "flame", that are very cold. Touching them sends chills down the spine.</GhostBreasts.description>

  <GhostAnus.label>immaterial anus</GhostAnus.label>
  <GhostAnus.description>A translucent, almost intangible anus. Internally, it seems to be composed of a bluish-white "flame", that is very cold. Penetrating it sends chills down the spine.</GhostAnus.description>


  <!-- Necro -->

  <NecroPenis.label>decayed penis</NecroPenis.label>
  <NecroPenis.labelNoun>A decayed penis</NecroPenis.labelNoun>
  <NecroPenis.description>A penis that was obviously salvaged from what was left when it decayed. It is full of stiches, parts that did not belong and is mostly falling apart. Somehow it still works.</NecroPenis.description>

  <NecroVagina.label>decayed vagina</NecroVagina.label>
  <NecroVagina.labelNoun>A decayed vagina</NecroVagina.labelNoun>
  <NecroVagina.description>A vagina that was salvaged from what remained after decaying. Its full of stiches, sometimes there's more than one hole to get into. Its insides are as cold as a grave.</NecroVagina.description>

  <NecroAnus.label>decayed anus</NecroAnus.label>
  <NecroAnus.labelNoun>A decayed anus</NecroAnus.labelNoun>
  <NecroAnus.description>An anus that was salvaged from what was left after decaying. Its insides are as cold as a grave.</NecroAnus.description>

  <NecroBreasts.label>decayed breasts</NecroBreasts.label>
  <NecroBreasts.labelNoun>A pair of decayed breasts</NecroBreasts.labelNoun>
  <NecroBreasts.description>A pair of breasts that where obviously salvaged from what was left after decaying. There's stiches all around, multiple nipples, extra patches of skin, and some other times, no skin at all. Sometimes there's not even boobs left.</NecroBreasts.description>


</LanguageData>