<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <HorsePenis.label>equine penis</HorsePenis.label>
  <HorsePenis.description>A large penis that telescopically extends from the shaft, leaving a ring of skin in the middle. The flat head flares out during the climax.</HorsePenis.description>

  <HorseVagina.label>equine vagina</HorseVagina.label>
  <HorseVagina.description>A vagina with a gapping and deep opening, and a large clitoris that usually peeks out when erect. The outer lips form a straight, thin slit when closed.</HorseVagina.description>

  <CatPenis.label>feline penis</CatPenis.label>
  <CatPenis.description>A penis with a pointy, strawberry-shaped head that is covered in tiny barbs. The barbs stimulate the walls of the lover's holes during sex.</CatPenis.description>

  <CatVagina.label>feline vagina</CatVagina.label>
  <CatVagina.description>A relatively small, but deep vagina. The clitoris is hidden inside, close to the opening. Fluffy.</CatVagina.description>

  <DogPenis.label>canine penis</DogPenis.label>
  <DogPenis.description>A penis that has a bulbous knot at the base. If fully inserted, the know will lock both lovers together for a long time.</DogPenis.description>

  <DogVagina.label>canine vagina</DogVagina.label>
  <DogVagina.description>A vagina with two holes: one is the vaginal opening, the other hides the clitoris. During heat the lips swell up, giving it the shape of a peach.</DogVagina.description>

  <DragonPenis.label>dragon penis</DragonPenis.label>
  <DragonPenis.description>A large and thick penis that is covered in scaly plates on the underside, and large barbs around the head. At its base there is a bulbous knot that locks it inside when fully inserted.</DragonPenis.description>

  <DragonVagina.label>dragon vagina</DragonVagina.label>
  <DragonVagina.description>A gaping vagina that is protected by though and scaly outer lips.</DragonVagina.description>

  <RaccoonPenis.label>procyonine penis</RaccoonPenis.label>
  <RaccoonPenis.description>A thin penis with a small round head. The bone the supports the shaft has a prominent 'S' curve.</RaccoonPenis.description>

  <HemiPenis.label>hemipenis</HemiPenis.label>
  <HemiPenis.description>A small pair of symmetrical penises, which are often covered in tiny barbs. Each penis has its semen production system, thus can orgasm independently. They are used only for sex and nothing else.</HemiPenis.description>

  <CrocodilianPenis.label>crocodilian penis</CrocodilianPenis.label>
  <CrocodilianPenis.description>A penis with a thick bulbous base, a rigid, bony shaft and a bulbous head. Due to the bone, it never gets flaccid, it just hides inside the body when not in use.</CrocodilianPenis.description>

  <NarrowVagina.label>narrow vagina</NarrowVagina.label>
  <NarrowVagina.description>A rather deep but very thin vagina.</NarrowVagina.description>

  <NeedlePenis.label>needle-like penis</NeedlePenis.label>
  <NeedlePenis.description>A very long, but also very thin penis that telescopically extends from the shaft.</NeedlePenis.description>

  <RodentVagina.label>rodent vagina</RodentVagina.label>
  <RodentVagina.description>A tiny vagina built for the bare minimum of functions.</RodentVagina.description>

  <RodentPenis.label>rodent penis</RodentPenis.label>
  <RodentPenis.description>A tiny penis built for the bare minimum of functions.</RodentPenis.description>

  <CloacalPenis.label>cloacal penis</CloacalPenis.label>
  <CloacalPenis.description>A male sex organ hidden inside the body. During sex, the hole is rubbed against the partner's in a genital "kiss", until sperm comes out.It shares its hole with the excretory organs.</CloacalPenis.description>

  <CloacalVagina.label>cloacal vagina</CloacalVagina.label>
  <CloacalVagina.description>A female, egg laying sex organ that shares its hole with the excretory organs.</CloacalVagina.description>

  <UdderBreasts.label>udder</UdderBreasts.label>
  <UdderBreasts.description>A group of four breasts with large nipples.</UdderBreasts.description>

  <CloacalAnus.label>cloacal anus</CloacalAnus.label>
  <CloacalAnus.description>An anus that share its hole with the reproductive organs.</CloacalAnus.description>


</LanguageData>